thecoveteur.com 2016-05-30

# Privacy Policy - The Coveteur

This Privacy Policy describes how The Coveteur Inc. (“we”/”us”) collects, stores, uses and distributes information when you visit our website, www.thecoveteur.com (the “Website”) and/or make purchases through our website or participate in contests offered by us. In addition to this Privacy Policy, you must read and agree to our Terms of Use when using the Website, including when ordering and buying goods online through the Website.

**Personal Information: What we Collect.**

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website unless you voluntarily provide this information, for example by creating an account, ordering products, submitting entries to contests, sending queries, comments or other feedback about the Website to us at http://thecoveteur.com/contact. Personal information collected in these cases may include your name, contact details, email address, telephone number, shipping and billing address, items purchased and other information which would be useful or necessary to process your orders (if applicable), provide customer support, allow you to use our website and send you communications such as newsletters (if you have opted to receive the same) and updates on your product orders.

It is always your choice whether to provide personal information to us and by doing so,  **you acknowledge and agree that you are giving us your consent to use that information to respond**  to your requests, to contact you and to provide information about our products, services and opportunities ( **see further:** _ **  Communications from The Coveteu**_r below). In relation to personal information provided by you in connection with a job listing, we will use that information for the purpose of assessing your application.

**Third Party Sources.**

If you have liked us on Facebook or interact with us through other social media sites, we may have access to some personal information about you (e.g. your name and the posts you have liked) that is made available on those third party sites. We will only use that data in an aggregated fashion to review and improve the Website and our services.

**Automatic Collection of Information.**

We automatically collects certain statistical and other data about visitors use or visits to the Website. This information includes IP addresses, statistics on pages viewed, web browsers and operating systems. This information is not personal information and is used by us to improve the Website and our services.

**Cookies.**

The Website uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies for other purposes such as site personalization. You can reject cookies and still browse the Website, however it will disable the ability for the site to recognize your cart, your account and any personalization efforts. We use this information to provide services to you, to measure and improve those services and to provide customer support. We may also use the information to detect and prevent unlawful activities.

**Communications from The Coveteur.**

Some messages from us are automatically sent when you open an account with us, place an order (including notification emails regarding the status of your order) or if we choose to email updates to this Policy or our Terms of Use. These communications cannot be opted out of by you unless you close your account. However, certain communications are optional (eg. if we make the option available to receive newsletters or product line updates from the Website) and can be opted-in and out of at your discretion. If we plan to use your Personal Information in future for any other purposes not identified above, we will only do so after informing you by updating this Privacy Policy. See further the section of this Privacy Policy entitled ‘ _ **Amendment of this Policy**_ ’.

**Advertisements.**

Advertisements appearing on the Website may be delivered by us or one or more third-party web advertisers. These third party web advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertisement server operated by that third party to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. Accordingly, advertisement servers may compile information about where or whether you viewed their advertisements and which advertisements you clicked on. This information allows web advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. The Privacy Policy applies to cookies placed on your computer by us, but does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party web advertisers. For the privacy practices of such third-party web advertisers, you should consult the applicable privacy policy for the relevant third-party web advertiser(s).

**Protecting Your Security.**

We take technical, contractual and administrative steps designed to protect your Personal Information. For example, we reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are also responsible for helping to protect the security of your Personal Information. For instance, never give out your password, remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished using the Website.

**Retention.**

We will keep your Personal Information for as long as it remains necessary for the identified purpose or as required by law, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. We may retain certain data as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you request that your name be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your Personal Information due to technological and legal constraints.

**Amendment of this Policy.**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy in the future, we will post an appropriate notice on the home page of the Website. Any non-material change (such as clarifications) to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date the change is posted and any material changes will become effective 30 days from their posting on the Website. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all Personal Information that we have about you. The date on which the latest update was made is indicated at the top of this document. We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Website signifies your acceptance of any changes.

**Access and Accuracy.**

You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you in order to verify the Personal Information we have collected in respect to you and to have a general account of our uses of that information. Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information although in certain limited circumstances, we may not be able to make all relevant information available to you such as where that information also pertains to another user. In such circumstances we will provide reasons for the denial to you upon request. We will endeavor to deal with all requests for access and modifications in a timely manner.

We will make every reasonable effort to keep your Personal Information accurate and up-to-date, and we will provide you with mechanisms to update, correct, delete or add to your Personal Information as appropriate. As appropriate, this amended Personal Information will be transmitted to those parties to which we are permitted to disclose your information. Having accurate Personal Information about you enables us to give you the best possible service.

**Contact Us.**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement and/or our practices in relation to data, please contact us at customersupport@thecoveteur.com.

Wake up to Louboutins with our newsletter.

Sign up Already!

It's the internet equivalent of a friendship bracelet.
